{
  "level": "A1",
  "oral_questions": [
    {
      "answer": "https://placements.s3.eu-central.stackpathstorage.com/audio-recordings/recording-1629208261256.webm?X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&X-Amz-Credential=WFCHCVI7NWJ45O02VZRI%2F20210817%2Feu-central-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&X-Amz-Date=20210817T135101Z&X-Amz-Expires=900&X-Amz-Signature=9bb1d00f0778e90a4ff6dafc098627b6214e9266c8065f0b161ef5494dda1a95&X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&x-id=GetObject"
    },
    {
      "answer": "https://placements.s3.eu-central.stackpathstorage.com/audio-recordings/recording-1629208266090.webm?X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&X-Amz-Credential=WFCHCVI7NWJ45O02VZRI%2F20210817%2Feu-central-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&X-Amz-Date=20210817T135106Z&X-Amz-Expires=900&X-Amz-Signature=4cb628dcc479e5ad19c89aac6a644fc3ba3b43574bd1ceff1f8899f3aac3c585&X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&x-id=GetObject"
    },
    {
      "answer": "https://placements.s3.eu-central.stackpathstorage.com/audio-recordings/recording-1629208269135.webm?X-Amz-Algorithm=AWS4-HMAC-SHA256&X-Amz-Content-Sha256=UNSIGNED-PAYLOAD&X-Amz-Credential=WFCHCVI7NWJ45O02VZRI%2F20210817%2Feu-central-1%2Fs3%2Faws4_request&X-Amz-Date=20210817T135109Z&X-Amz-Expires=900&X-Amz-Signature=2037d1992cf9650a375952da941e68c920d131c651df85bf41ad1331dd8ced21&X-Amz-SignedHeaders=host&x-id=GetObject"
    }
  ],
  "contact": {
    "name": "Bernardo Louren√ßo",
    "email": "top_memes@gmail.com",
    "phone": "+351960435112"
  },
  "written_questions": [
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "John made a sandwich _ he was hungry.",
      "choices": ["so", "because", "and", "but"],
      "correct": "because",
      "answer": "because"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "What time is it? It's _ (11:15).",
      "choices": [
        "quarter to eleven",
        "eleven and fifteen",
        "eleven fifteen",
        "fifteen to eleven"
      ],
      "correct": "eleven fifteen",
      "answer": "eleven and fifteen"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "_ your husband do? He's a doctor.",
      "choices": ["What job", "What does", "Which job", "Where works"],
      "correct": "What does",
      "answer": "What does"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "My grandparents live in the countryside. _ have a big garden.",
      "choices": ["Them", "Their", "There", "They"],
      "correct": "They",
      "answer": "Them"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "_ did you find the answer? I looked on the Internet.",
      "choices": ["Why", "What", "How", "When"],
      "correct": "How",
      "answer": "Why"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "I don't want _ bed. I'm not tired.",
      "choices": ["going", "to go to", "go", "go to"],
      "correct": "to go to",
      "answer": "going"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "Please _ your room today.",
      "choices": ["you clean", "clean", "cleaning", "to clean"],
      "correct": "clean",
      "answer": "you clean"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "Every day, Jane has _ piece of cake after dinner.",
      "choices": ["the", "a", "(nothing)", "some"],
      "correct": "a",
      "answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "_ weather is wonderful today.",
      "choices": ["An", "A", "The", "(nothing)"],
      "correct": "The",
      "answer": "An"
    },
    {
      "level": "A1",
      "question": "My brother is very _. He plays basketball well.",
      "choices": ["expensive", "high", "tall", "long"],
      "correct": "tall",
      "answer": "expensive"
    }
  ]
}
